cbsl.gov.lk 2019-06-04

# Privacy Policy Statement | Central Bank of Sri Lanka

## Central Bank of Sri Lanka's Commitment and Assurance to Privacy

The Central Bank of Sri Lanka (the Bank) respects the privacy of the individuals who interact with this website or whose information that may collect indirectly by this website, and is committed to protecting the privacy of those individuals. This Privacy Policy sets out some key information about the Bank's approach to privacy.

## Personal Information

We do not collect personal information such as names, ages and addresses when you visit our website unless you choose to provide it to us. If you do choose to provide personal information to the Bank, it is only used for the purpose for which you gave it to us.

### If You Provide Personal Information

You may decide to send us information, including personally identifiable information. The information you supply, through sending an email message is maintained by us only for the purpose of working on your request or inquiry.

## Cookies

We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

## Links to other websites and interactions with third parties

This notice does not cover links to other websites or any interactions you have with third parties. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of all other websites you visit and third parties with whom you interact.

## Information Security

If you share any personal information with us, we will take proper steps to protect that information from unauthorized access or disclosure.

This site is accessible only through SSL protocol and therefore all the information flows through an encrypted link between a server and you (client) protecting the transfer of data and information.

Our web servers collect website access information such as the IP addresses of visitors, the number of page visits and the number of times each file is downloaded or the time of day or location that people visit our webpages. We are using this information in aggregation to analyze the effectiveness of the Banks’s web-site for the purpose of further optimizing and enhancing our content and services.

## Enquiries and Complaints

If you would like more information about the Banks privacy and information practices, please contact us by:

Director Communications  
Central Bank of Sri Lanka,  
30, Janadhipathi Mawatha,  
Colombo 01, Sri Lanka

Email: [cbslgen@cbsl.lk](mailto:cbslgen@cbsl.lk)  
Tel: +94 11 2477418  
Fax: + 94 11 2346304
